# TYLER GRAY

TGRAY.IT@GMAIL.COM | 334.233.6931

JOHNTGRAY.COM

### EXPERTISE

WEB DESIGN & DEVELOPMENT

SEO + ANALYTICS

WINDOWS / LINUX

### EDUCATION

ASSOCIATES DEGREE
CIS | FOCUS IN
PROGRAMING & WEB
Trenholm State Technical College
2009 - 2012

# SKILLS

HTML5 / CSS3

JAVASCRIPT JQUERY

C# / ASP.NET

JAVA

PHP

SQL

RESPONSIVE DESIGN

### PROFILE

Born and raised in central Alabama, I have over five years of web design and development experience in the professional community. Furthermore, I am proficient in tech support, Windows and Linux server management, and SEO + Google Analytics. I am seeking a position with a progressive technology company to expand my knowledge and be an asset to your company.

# EXPERIENCE

#### SYSTEM ANALYST

ASE Credit Union / July 2015 - Present

Designed and developed new credit union website. Created web applications using html5, css3, c# / asp.net, Java, and javascript + jquery. Coordinated with marketing to insure consistent branding across ASE Credit Union websites. Developed many SQL reports and queries for management and staff. Implemented high security software preventing ddos attacks and other malicious intrusions. Provided technical support to resolve computer software and hardware related issues.

# VICE PRESIDENT | BOARD OF DIRECTORS

Friends of the Forts / 2014 – Present

Developed rebranding of Friends of The Forts. Launched and manage multiple social media channels. Designed and developed a website for Fort Toulouse – Fort Jackson State Park. Coordinated with third-party companies in the production of print media and promotional items. Rebranding was successful in increasing membership and public awareness of the organization.

# TYLER GRAY

TGRAY.IT@GMAIL.COM | 334.233.6931

JOHNTGRAY.COM

# REFERENCES

MATTHEW ISBELL
INSURANCE AGENT | NASB
3625 ASHTON CT, GULF
SHORES, AL 36542
334-391-4053

RUSSELL MARTIN ASSISTANT MANAGER | HYUNDAI 165 POPLAR GROVE DR. WETUMPKA, 36093 334-451-0486

TIM LAWRENCE
MANAGER | PEACHES N' CLEAN
78 VILLAGE KNOLL.
WETUMPKA, 36093
334-549-4880

# SOCIAL

TGRAY.IT



@JTGRY



@JTGRY



**JTGRY** 



# EXPERIENCE

#### FREELANCE WEB DESIGNER

2008 – Present

Designed and developed dozens of websites for clients and personal projects using HTML5, CSS3, JS + JQUERY. Each site I build uses the latest technology and design techniques. Please visit johntgray.com to see my latest work.

### SYSTEM SUPPORT SPECIALIST

ASE Credit Union / May 2013 - July 2015

Administered Windows, Linux, and Unix servers, while supporting credit union related systems. Provided technical support to resolve computer software and hardware related issues. Managed and updated credit union website. Designed and developed an in-house company web portal which provided secure access to company programs and applications. Assisted in implementation of a new Keystone core banking system, while also providing training for credit union personnel.

### PC SUPPORT TECH

ASE Credit Union / August 2010 - May 2013

Coordinated with Marketing to design and developed website for ASE Credit Union. Provided technical support and resolved computer software and hardware related issues. Also, assisted installing and supporting credit union servers and systems. Provided training to credit union personnel on Windows 7, Microsoft applications, and Spectrum core banking system.

### PACKAGE LOADER

UPS / September 2008 – July 2010

Processed and distributed thousands of packages in a very fast paced and physically demanding work environment.